To ensure my agent has the necessary
context to use the open- source
libraries I've chosen to use, I must
make sure I've installed all the usage
specifications for every direct
dependency in my project.
I'm going to ask Claude Code to discover
which direct dependencies I'm using and
find a usage spec for each one in turn.
Claude Code uses Tessle's MCP search
tool to look for each usage spec in
Tessle spec registry, attempting to
match the package name we're using in my
project with a corresponding usage spec.
Once matched, it will install the
correct version them from the spec
registry to my local file system again
via the Tessle MCP server.
On my local file system, the Tessle.json
file shows the project dependencies for
which we have matched usage specs. The
knowledge MD maps these to the local
specs we have now installed on our file
system stored in my project. The
index.mmd file serves as the root usage
spec linking to all other usage specs
for that open source library.
I've now given my agent the knowledge
and context it needs to code effectively
with all my project dependencies using
Tessle's usage specs.